https://williamsav.com/privacy-policy/

Introduction
Williams AV recognizes you may have questions about our collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information (“PII”) you send to us at Williams AV, Williams Sound and Pointmaker and other information we collect during the course of your visit to www.williamssound.com and www.pointmaker.com (“Site”).  We value our relationship with you and want to help keep your experience on our Sites secure, enjoyable, efficient and easy.ContactIf you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy (“Policy”), please contact us at info@williamssound.com.What we CollectWe only collect PII from you when you choose to provide it to us so you can receive services from us.PII is information that identifies you individually and consists of your name, business name, mailing address, phone number, email address, credit card number, your resume and financial information.We also collect Non-Personal Information (“NPI”) from you. NPI is information which cannot be easily used to personally identify you and includes, for example, the type of web browser you use to access our Site, the URL of the previous website you visited, clickstream patterns, your ISP, your operating system and your IP address.PII and NPI are collectively referred to as “Information.”How we use the Information we CollectPII may be used for our business purposes and in a manner consistent with this Policy.  This use includes, but is not limited to, maintaining, evaluating and improving our sales, services to you, and our Site.NPI is used to track your usage of the Site and other internal purposes, such as Site maintenance, evaluation and user-experience.Our Role as a Data ProcessorIn the provision of our various services, we act as a processor for the PII that you choose to provide to us.Disclosure to Third PartiesWe reserve the right to disclose any Information we collect to third parties we directly work with, such as dealers selling our products (“Authorized Representatives”). These third parties are our Authorized Representatives.Note that disclosing PII, product or purchase information to Authorized Representatives is required for the purchase of a product or submitting and processing a repair request.Access and Correction of PIIYou may review and edit your PII at any time. If you are unable to make the change yourself, please contact us at helpdesk@williamssound.com. We may require that you validate your identity before any change is made.Deletion of PIIYou may submit a request to delete your PII at helpdesk@williamssound.com. Before updates are made through this means, appropriate validation of your identity will be made.Protecting PIIWe strive to maintain reasonable data security measures. However, no security measures are invulnerable to attack. We are not responsible for the security of your PII that you transmit to us over networks that we do not control, including, but not limited to, wireless networks.Taking your PIIYou may request that we provide you with the PII you have provided to us in a machine-readable data file in a standard format (such as ‘csv’). If you would like to receive this file, please contact us at helpdesk@williamssound.com.Disclosure to SuccessorsWe may disclose Information to any successor-in-interest of ours, such as, but not limited to, a company that acquires us.Disclosure to Unaffiliated Third PartiesWe may disclose PII to prevent an emergency, to protect or enforce the rights of a third party, as required or permitted by law (including, but not limited to, compliance with a subpoena).We do not disclose information to other unaffiliated third parties – we will never sell your PII to a third-party.Length of PII StorageWe will keep your PII for as long as is necessary for the continued provision of services to you, or where we have a legitimate interest to continue doing so. For instance, your warranty information will be stored for the lifetime of the product you purchased from us.Privacy Policy ChangesWe reserve the right to modify, add or remove any terms and conditions in this Policy without prior notice or liability to you.Any changes we make will be effective immediately following posting on the Site.If you are subscribed to our mailing list with a valid e-mail address, you will receive an announcement from us indicating an update to the Policy has been made.Children’s PrivacyOur Site and services are not intended for users younger than 13 years of age.  Accordingly, we will not knowingly collect or use any PII from children that we know are under 13 years of age.  In addition, we will delete any Information in our database that we know originates from a child under the age of 13.Cookies and Other TechnologiesWe use cookies in this Site.  The cookie settings on this Site are set to ‘allow all cookies’.If you continue using the Site without changing these settings, you consent to the use of cookies. You can, however, change your browser settings at any time to control the use of cookies. For more information, please refer to your browser settings.Click here to opt-out of Google Analytics. We do not store PII in Google Analytics cookies.Data Controller and Contact InformationThe data controller of this Site website is Williams AV, LLC.You can contact us at:10300 Valley View RoadEden Prairie, MN 55344USAphone: 952-943-2252fax: 952-943-2174Data Protection OfficerFor questions about your PII, or to lodge a complaint, contact:Information Systems ManagerPhone: 952-224-7782E-mail:dpo@williamsav.comOther ContactIf you have any general questions or concerns about this Site, or this Policy, please feel free to contact us at info@williamssound.com.
©Copyright 2020 – Williams AV, LLC
Williams Sound, Williams Sound Helping People Hear, “W” graphic, Pointmaker, Williams AV, Pocketalker, Motiva, SoundPlus, Personal PA and Hearing Helper are registered trademarks of Williams AV, LLC.
No claim is made to the exclusive right to use “Sound”, apart from the mark as shown.
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
CONTACT US
10300 Valley View Road
Eden Prairie, MN 55344
USA
Intl:+1.952.943.2252
ph:800.328.6190
SUBSCRIBE
Receive our latest updates to your inbox! Enter your email address:
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Read MoreCookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Video Popup
×
